hoganstand.com 2019-12-18

# HoganStand GAA Football and Hurling

## Privacy Policy

Hoganstand.com takes your right to privacy seriously. Our aim is to comply with the obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

By visiting hoganstand.com you are accepting the terms of this website’s privacy policy. If you do not accept the terms of this website’s privacy policy, your only remedy is to stop visiting this website. This website contains links to other websites in the form of advertisements or links. This privacy policy does not apply to these other websites.

**What information do we collect?**

When you visit our website, we collect information based on your computer, such as cookies, IP address, browsing system and device. You can disable cookies on your computer if you wish. If you register for our forum, we collect your email address.

**What do we use your information for and do we use cookies?**

This information helps keep you logged into forums, so you don't have to log in every time you visit our site. If we have a survey, it helps remember is you have already filled it in. They also help us operate our polls, so that you can't vote more than once. The information helps improve your experience on our site and decide what type of advertisement you will see and also how often you might see them, from us or third party advertising providers. The information helps us remember you if you have used social media to share stories so you don't have to keep logging in. This information help us with Analytics, so we know what our audience are reading and how they use our site. These cookies don't collect information that identifies you. The information collected is anonymous and is grouped with the information from everyone else’s cookies. You can restrict or disable the use of cookies in your web experience but it is important to note that you will lose some functions of a website if you do so. Your browser's help screen allows you to change your cookie settings.

**How do we secure your information?**

We make every effort to protect your information and constantly review and implement our security management protocols. We have numerous layers of security in place and take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your data. The nature of the internet is such that we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and your do so at your own risk.

**Do we disclose any information to third parties?**

We do not supply or sell your information to third parties and all information we collect is used solely in relation to hoganstand.com 

**How can I update my information?**

Registered users of our forum can change their passwords on our site or make changes to their forum account by contacting our Data Protection Officer (contact details are at the bottom of this page).

**Contacting us**

It is our aim to comply with the guidelines of the Data Commissioner of Ireland and GDPR. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at:

**Data Protection Officer,**

Hoganstand.com,  
DG Press Ltd,  
Kells Business Park,  
Cavan Road,  
Kells  
County Meath.

t 046 92 41923

Updated 24/05/2018

* * *
